{
  "uniqueId": "anagrams4",
  "name": "Anagrams Length 4 Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Unscramable the below word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "IMAGE",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "RANDOMIZE_QUESTION_CHARACTERS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "QUESTION_AND_ANSWER_LINK_ANSWER",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "answerCompareStrategy": "STRICT",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "abbe",
      "answer": "abbe"
    },
    {
      "question": "abed",
      "answer": "abed"
    },
    {
      "question": "abet",
      "answer": "abet"
    },
    {
      "question": "able",
      "answer": "able"
    },
    {
      "question": "ache",
      "answer": "ache"
    },
    {
      "question": "acid",
      "answer": "acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "acne",
      "answer": "acne"
    },
    {
      "question": "acre",
      "answer": "acre"
    },
    {
      "question": "aery",
      "answer": "aery"
    },
    {
      "question": "afar",
      "answer": "afar"
    },
    {
      "question": "aged",
      "answer": "aged"
    },
    {
      "question": "aide",
      "answer": "aide"
    },
    {
      "question": "akin",
      "answer": "akin"
    },
    {
      "question": "alas",
      "answer": "alas"
    },
    {
      "question": "alga",
      "answer": "alga"
    },
    {
      "question": "ally",
      "answer": "ally"
    },
    {
      "question": "alms",
      "answer": "alms"
    },
    {
      "question": "also",
      "answer": "also"
    },
    {
      "question": "alto",
      "answer": "alto"
    },
    {
      "question": "amen",
      "answer": "amen"
    },
    {
      "question": "amid",
      "answer": "amid"
    },
    {
      "question": "anew",
      "answer": "anew"
    },
    {
      "question": "ante",
      "answer": "ante"
    },
    {
      "question": "apex",
      "answer": "apex"
    },
    {
      "question": "arch",
      "answer": "arch"
    },
    {
      "question": "area",
      "answer": "area"
    },
    {
      "question": "aria",
      "answer": "aria"
    },
    {
      "question": "arid",
      "answer": "arid"
    },
    {
      "question": "army",
      "answer": "army"
    },
    {
      "question": "arty",
      "answer": "arty"
    },
    {
      "question": "atom",
      "answer": "atom"
    },
    {
      "question": "auld",
      "answer": "auld"
    },
    {
      "question": "aunt",
      "answer": "aunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "aura",
      "answer": "aura"
    },
    {
      "question": "auto",
      "answer": "auto"
    },
    {
      "question": "avid",
      "answer": "avid"
    },
    {
      "question": "away",
      "answer": "away"
    },
    {
      "question": "awry",
      "answer": "awry"
    },
    {
      "question": "axis",
      "answer": "axis"
    },
    {
      "question": "babe",
      "answer": "babe"
    },
    {
      "question": "baby",
      "answer": "baby"
    },
    {
      "question": "back",
      "answer": "back"
    },
    {
      "question": "bade",
      "answer": "bade"
    },
    {
      "question": "baht",
      "answer": "baht"
    },
    {
      "question": "bait",
      "answer": "bait"
    },
    {
      "question": "bake",
      "answer": "bake"
    },
    {
      "question": "bald",
      "answer": "bald"
    },
    {
      "question": "bale",
      "answer": "bale"
    },
    {
      "question": "balk",
      "answer": "balk"
    },
    {
      "question": "ball",
      "answer": "ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "balm",
      "answer": "balm"
    },
    {
      "question": "band",
      "answer": "band"
    },
    {
      "question": "bane",
      "answer": "bane"
    },
    {
      "question": "bang",
      "answer": "bang"
    },
    {
      "question": "bank",
      "answer": "bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "bard",
      "answer": "bard"
    },
    {
      "question": "bare",
      "answer": "bare"
    },
    {
      "question": "bark",
      "answer": "bark"
    },
    {
      "question": "barn",
      "answer": "barn"
    },
    {
      "question": "base",
      "answer": "base"
    },
    {
      "question": "bash",
      "answer": "bash"
    },
    {
      "question": "bask",
      "answer": "bask"
    },
    {
      "question": "bast",
      "answer": "bast"
    },
    {
      "question": "bate",
      "answer": "bate"
    },
    {
      "question": "bath",
      "answer": "bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "bead",
      "answer": "bead"
    },
    {
      "question": "beak",
      "answer": "beak"
    },
    {
      "question": "beam",
      "answer": "beam"
    },
    {
      "question": "bean",
      "answer": "bean"
    },
    {
      "question": "bear",
      "answer": "bear"
    },
    {
      "question": "beat",
      "answer": "beat"
    },
    {
      "question": "beef",
      "answer": "beef"
    },
    {
      "question": "been",
      "answer": "been"
    },
    {
      "question": "beer",
      "answer": "beer"
    },
    {
      "question": "beet",
      "answer": "beet"
    },
    {
      "question": "bell",
      "answer": "bell"
    },
    {
      "question": "belt",
      "answer": "belt"
    },
    {
      "question": "bend",
      "answer": "bend"
    },
    {
      "question": "bent",
      "answer": "bent"
    },
    {
      "question": "best",
      "answer": "best"
    },
    {
      "question": "bias",
      "answer": "bias"
    },
    {
      "question": "bike",
      "answer": "bike"
    },
    {
      "question": "bile",
      "answer": "bile"
    },
    {
      "question": "bill",
      "answer": "bill"
    },
    {
      "question": "bind",
      "answer": "bind"
    },
    {
      "question": "bird",
      "answer": "bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "bite",
      "answer": "bite"
    },
    {
      "question": "bloc",
      "answer": "bloc"
    },
    {
      "question": "blot",
      "answer": "blot"
    },
    {
      "question": "blow",
      "answer": "blow"
    },
    {
      "question": "blue",
      "answer": "blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "boat",
      "answer": "boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "bode",
      "answer": "bode"
    },
    {
      "question": "body",
      "answer": "body"
    },
    {
      "question": "boil",
      "answer": "boil"
    },
    {
      "question": "bold",
      "answer": "bold"
    },
    {
      "question": "bole",
      "answer": "bole"
    },
    {
      "question": "bolt",
      "answer": "bolt"
    },
    {
      "question": "bomb",
      "answer": "bomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "bond",
      "answer": "bond"
    },
    {
      "question": "bone",
      "answer": "bone"
    },
    {
      "question": "bony",
      "answer": "bony"
    },
    {
      "question": "book",
      "answer": "book"
    },
    {
      "question": "boom",
      "answer": "boom"
    },
    {
      "question": "boon",
      "answer": "boon"
    },
    {
      "question": "boot",
      "answer": "boot"
    },
    {
      "question": "bore",
      "answer": "bore"
    },
    {
      "question": "born",
      "answer": "born"
    },
    {
      "question": "boss",
      "answer": "boss"
    },
    {
      "question": "both",
      "answer": "both"
    },
    {
      "question": "bout",
      "answer": "bout"
    },
    {
      "question": "bowl",
      "answer": "bowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "brad",
      "answer": "brad"
    },
    {
      "question": "brae",
      "answer": "brae"
    },
    {
      "question": "brag",
      "answer": "brag"
    },
    {
      "question": "bran",
      "answer": "bran"
    },
    {
      "question": "brim",
      "answer": "brim"
    },
    {
      "question": "brow",
      "answer": "brow"
    },
    {
      "question": "buck",
      "answer": "buck"
    },
    {
      "question": "buff",
      "answer": "buff"
    },
    {
      "question": "bulb",
      "answer": "bulb"
    },
    {
      "question": "bulk",
      "answer": "bulk"
    },
    {
      "question": "bull",
      "answer": "bull"
    },
    {
      "question": "bump",
      "answer": "bump"
    },
    {
      "question": "bunk",
      "answer": "bunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "burn",
      "answer": "burn"
    },
    {
      "question": "bury",
      "answer": "bury"
    },
    {
      "question": "bush",
      "answer": "bush"
    },
    {
      "question": "bust",
      "answer": "bust"
    },
    {
      "question": "busy",
      "answer": "busy"
    },
    {
      "question": "buzz",
      "answer": "buzz"
    },
    {
      "question": "cafe",
      "answer": "cafe"
    },
    {
      "question": "cage",
      "answer": "cage"
    },
    {
      "question": "cake",
      "answer": "cake"
    },
    {
      "question": "calf",
      "answer": "calf"
    },
    {
      "question": "calk",
      "answer": "calk"
    },
    {
      "question": "call",
      "answer": "call"
    },
    {
      "question": "calm",
      "answer": "calm"
    },
    {
      "question": "camp",
      "answer": "camp"
    },
    {
      "question": "cane",
      "answer": "cane"
    },
    {
      "question": "cant",
      "answer": "cant"
    },
    {
      "question": "cape",
      "answer": "cape"
    },
    {
      "question": "card",
      "answer": "card"
    },
    {
      "question": "care",
      "answer": "care"
    },
    {
      "question": "carp",
      "answer": "carp"
    },
    {
      "question": "cart",
      "answer": "cart"
    },
    {
      "question": "case",
      "answer": "case"
    },
    {
      "question": "cash",
      "answer": "cash"
    },
    {
      "question": "cask",
      "answer": "cask"
    },
    {
      "question": "cast",
      "answer": "cast"
    },
    {
      "question": "cave",
      "answer": "cave"
    },
    {
      "question": "cell",
      "answer": "cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "cent",
      "answer": "cent"
    },
    {
      "question": "chap",
      "answer": "chap"
    },
    {
      "question": "char",
      "answer": "char"
    },
    {
      "question": "chat",
      "answer": "chat"
    },
    {
      "question": "chef",
      "answer": "chef"
    },
    {
      "question": "chew",
      "answer": "chew"
    },
    {
      "question": "chic",
      "answer": "chic"
    },
    {
      "question": "chin",
      "answer": "chin"
    },
    {
      "question": "chip",
      "answer": "chip"
    },
    {
      "question": "chit",
      "answer": "chit"
    },
    {
      "question": "chop",
      "answer": "chop"
    },
    {
      "question": "chum",
      "answer": "chum"
    },
    {
      "question": "cite",
      "answer": "cite"
    },
    {
      "question": "city",
      "answer": "city"
    },
    {
      "question": "clam",
      "answer": "clam"
    },
    {
      "question": "clan",
      "answer": "clan"
    },
    {
      "question": "clap",
      "answer": "clap"
    },
    {
      "question": "clay",
      "answer": "clay"
    },
    {
      "question": "clip",
      "answer": "clip"
    },
    {
      "question": "clod",
      "answer": "clod"
    },
    {
      "question": "clog",
      "answer": "clog"
    },
    {
      "question": "clot",
      "answer": "clot"
    },
    {
      "question": "club",
      "answer": "club"
    },
    {
      "question": "clue",
      "answer": "clue"
    },
    {
      "question": "coal",
      "answer": "coal"
    },
    {
      "question": "coat",
      "answer": "coat"
    },
    {
      "question": "coax",
      "answer": "coax"
    },
    {
      "question": "code",
      "answer": "code"
    },
    {
      "question": "coil",
      "answer": "coil"
    },
    {
      "question": "coin",
      "answer": "coin"
    },
    {
      "question": "coke",
      "answer": "coke"
    },
    {
      "question": "cola",
      "answer": "cola"
    },
    {
      "question": "cold",
      "answer": "cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "colt",
      "answer": "colt"
    },
    {
      "question": "coma",
      "answer": "coma"
    },
    {
      "question": "comb",
      "answer": "comb"
    },
    {
      "question": "come",
      "answer": "come"
    },
    {
      "question": "cone",
      "answer": "cone"
    },
    {
      "question": "cook",
      "answer": "cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "cool",
      "answer": "cool"
    },
    {
      "question": "coop",
      "answer": "coop"
    },
    {
      "question": "cope",
      "answer": "cope"
    },
    {
      "question": "copy",
      "answer": "copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "cord",
      "answer": "cord"
    },
    {
      "question": "core",
      "answer": "core"
    },
    {
      "question": "cork",
      "answer": "cork"
    },
    {
      "question": "corn",
      "answer": "corn"
    },
    {
      "question": "cost",
      "answer": "cost"
    },
    {
      "question": "cove",
      "answer": "cove"
    },
    {
      "question": "cozy",
      "answer": "cozy"
    },
    {
      "question": "crab",
      "answer": "crab"
    },
    {
      "question": "crew",
      "answer": "crew"
    },
    {
      "question": "crib",
      "answer": "crib"
    },
    {
      "question": "crop",
      "answer": "crop"
    },
    {
      "question": "crow",
      "answer": "crow"
    },
    {
      "question": "crux",
      "answer": "crux"
    },
    {
      "question": "cube",
      "answer": "cube"
    },
    {
      "question": "cuff",
      "answer": "cuff"
    },
    {
      "question": "cull",
      "answer": "cull"
    },
    {
      "question": "cult",
      "answer": "cult"
    },
    {
      "question": "curb",
      "answer": "curb"
    },
    {
      "question": "cure",
      "answer": "cure"
    },
    {
      "question": "curl",
      "answer": "curl"
    },
    {
      "question": "curt",
      "answer": "curt"
    },
    {
      "question": "cute",
      "answer": "cute"
    },
    {
      "question": "czar",
      "answer": "czar"
    },
    {
      "question": "daft",
      "answer": "daft"
    },
    {
      "question": "dale",
      "answer": "dale"
    },
    {
      "question": "damn",
      "answer": "damn"
    },
    {
      "question": "damp",
      "answer": "damp"
    },
    {
      "question": "dare",
      "answer": "dare"
    },
    {
      "question": "dark",
      "answer": "dark"
    },
    {
      "question": "darn",
      "answer": "darn"
    },
    {
      "question": "dart",
      "answer": "dart"
    },
    {
      "question": "dash",
      "answer": "dash"
    },
    {
      "question": "data",
      "answer": "data"
    },
    {
      "question": "date",
      "answer": "date"
    },
    {
      "question": "daub",
      "answer": "daub"
    },
    {
      "question": "dawn",
      "answer": "dawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "daze",
      "answer": "daze"
    },
    {
      "question": "dead",
      "answer": "dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "deaf",
      "answer": "deaf"
    },
    {
      "question": "deal",
      "answer": "deal"
    },
    {
      "question": "dean",
      "answer": "dean"
    },
    {
      "question": "dear",
      "answer": "dear"
    },
    {
      "question": "debt",
      "answer": "debt"
    },
    {
      "question": "deck",
      "answer": "deck"
    },
    {
      "question": "deed",
      "answer": "deed"
    },
    {
      "question": "deem",
      "answer": "deem"
    },
    {
      "question": "deep",
      "answer": "deep"
    },
    {
      "question": "deer",
      "answer": "deer"
    },
    {
      "question": "deft",
      "answer": "deft"
    },
    {
      "question": "defy",
      "answer": "defy"
    },
    {
      "question": "dent",
      "answer": "dent"
    },
    {
      "question": "deny",
      "answer": "deny"
    },
    {
      "question": "desk",
      "answer": "desk"
    },
    {
      "question": "dial",
      "answer": "dial"
    },
    {
      "question": "dice",
      "answer": "dice"
    },
    {
      "question": "diet",
      "answer": "diet"
    },
    {
      "question": "dike",
      "answer": "dike"
    },
    {
      "question": "dime",
      "answer": "dime"
    },
    {
      "question": "dine",
      "answer": "dine"
    },
    {
      "question": "dire",
      "answer": "dire"
    },
    {
      "question": "dirt",
      "answer": "dirt"
    },
    {
      "question": "dish",
      "answer": "dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "disk",
      "answer": "disk"
    },
    {
      "question": "diva",
      "answer": "diva"
    },
    {
      "question": "dive",
      "answer": "dive"
    },
    {
      "question": "dock",
      "answer": "dock"
    },
    {
      "question": "doll",
      "answer": "doll"
    },
    {
      "question": "dome",
      "answer": "dome"
    },
    {
      "question": "done",
      "answer": "done"
    },
    {
      "question": "doom",
      "answer": "doom"
    },
    {
      "question": "door",
      "answer": "door"
    },
    {
      "question": "dope",
      "answer": "dope"
    },
    {
      "question": "dose",
      "answer": "dose"
    },
    {
      "question": "dour",
      "answer": "dour"
    },
    {
      "question": "dove",
      "answer": "dove"
    },
    {
      "question": "down",
      "answer": "down"
    },
    {
      "question": "doze",
      "answer": "doze"
    },
    {
      "question": "drab",
      "answer": "drab"
    },
    {
      "question": "drag",
      "answer": "drag"
    },
    {
      "question": "draw",
      "answer": "draw"
    },
    {
      "question": "dray",
      "answer": "dray"
    },
    {
      "question": "drip",
      "answer": "drip"
    },
    {
      "question": "drop",
      "answer": "drop"
    },
    {
      "question": "drug",
      "answer": "drug"
    },
    {
      "question": "drum",
      "answer": "drum"
    },
    {
      "question": "dual",
      "answer": "dual"
    },
    {
      "question": "duck",
      "answer": "duck"
    },
    {
      "question": "duct",
      "answer": "duct"
    },
    {
      "question": "duel",
      "answer": "duel"
    },
    {
      "question": "duet",
      "answer": "duet"
    },
    {
      "question": "duke",
      "answer": "duke"
    },
    {
      "question": "dull",
      "answer": "dull"
    },
    {
      "question": "dumb",
      "answer": "dumb"
    },
    {
      "question": "dump",
      "answer": "dump"
    },
    {
      "question": "dune",
      "answer": "dune"
    },
    {
      "question": "dung",
      "answer": "dung"
    },
    {
      "question": "dusk",
      "answer": "dusk"
    },
    {
      "question": "dust",
      "answer": "dust"
    },
    {
      "question": "duty",
      "answer": "duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "each",
      "answer": "each"
    },
    {
      "question": "earl",
      "answer": "earl"
    },
    {
      "question": "earn",
      "answer": "earn"
    },
    {
      "question": "ease",
      "answer": "ease"
    },
    {
      "question": "east",
      "answer": "east"
    },
    {
      "question": "easy",
      "answer": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "echo",
      "answer": "echo"
    },
    {
      "question": "eddy",
      "answer": "eddy"
    },
    {
      "question": "edge",
      "answer": "edge"
    },
    {
      "question": "edit",
      "answer": "edit"
    },
    {
      "question": "elan",
      "answer": "elan"
    },
    {
      "question": "else",
      "answer": "else"
    },
    {
      "question": "emit",
      "answer": "emit"
    },
    {
      "question": "envy",
      "answer": "envy"
    },
    {
      "question": "epic",
      "answer": "epic"
    },
    {
      "question": "erst",
      "answer": "erst"
    },
    {
      "question": "etch",
      "answer": "etch"
    },
    {
      "question": "even",
      "answer": "even"
    },
    {
      "question": "ever",
      "answer": "ever"
    },
    {
      "question": "evil",
      "answer": "evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "ewer",
      "answer": "ewer"
    },
    {
      "question": "exit",
      "answer": "exit"
    },
    {
      "question": "face",
      "answer": "face"
    },
    {
      "question": "fact",
      "answer": "fact"
    },
    {
      "question": "fade",
      "answer": "fade"
    },
    {
      "question": "fail",
      "answer": "fail"
    },
    {
      "question": "fair",
      "answer": "fair"
    },
    {
      "question": "fake",
      "answer": "fake"
    },
    {
      "question": "fall",
      "answer": "fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "fame",
      "answer": "fame"
    },
    {
      "question": "fare",
      "answer": "fare"
    },
    {
      "question": "farm",
      "answer": "farm"
    },
    {
      "question": "fast",
      "answer": "fast"
    },
    {
      "question": "fate",
      "answer": "fate"
    },
    {
      "question": "fawn",
      "answer": "fawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "fear",
      "answer": "fear"
    },
    {
      "question": "feat",
      "answer": "feat"
    },
    {
      "question": "feed",
      "answer": "feed"
    },
    {
      "question": "feel",
      "answer": "feel"
    },
    {
      "question": "felt",
      "answer": "felt"
    },
    {
      "question": "fern",
      "answer": "fern"
    },
    {
      "question": "feud",
      "answer": "feud"
    },
    {
      "question": "fiat",
      "answer": "fiat"
    },
    {
      "question": "file",
      "answer": "file"
    },
    {
      "question": "fill",
      "answer": "fill"
    },
    {
      "question": "film",
      "answer": "film"
    },
    {
      "question": "find",
      "answer": "find"
    },
    {
      "question": "fine",
      "answer": "fine"
    },
    {
      "question": "fire",
      "answer": "fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "firm",
      "answer": "firm"
    },
    {
      "question": "fish",
      "answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "fist",
      "answer": "fist"
    },
    {
      "question": "five",
      "answer": "five"
    },
    {
      "question": "flag",
      "answer": "flag"
    },
    {
      "question": "flap",
      "answer": "flap"
    },
    {
      "question": "flat",
      "answer": "flat"
    },
    {
      "question": "flaw",
      "answer": "flaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "flea",
      "answer": "flea"
    },
    {
      "question": "flee",
      "answer": "flee"
    },
    {
      "question": "flex",
      "answer": "flex"
    },
    {
      "question": "flip",
      "answer": "flip"
    },
    {
      "question": "flit",
      "answer": "flit"
    },
    {
      "question": "flog",
      "answer": "flog"
    },
    {
      "question": "flop",
      "answer": "flop"
    },
    {
      "question": "flow",
      "answer": "flow"
    },
    {
      "question": "flue",
      "answer": "flue"
    },
    {
      "question": "flux",
      "answer": "flux"
    },
    {
      "question": "foal",
      "answer": "foal"
    },
    {
      "question": "foam",
      "answer": "foam"
    },
    {
      "question": "fold",
      "answer": "fold"
    },
    {
      "question": "folk",
      "answer": "folk"
    },
    {
      "question": "fond",
      "answer": "fond"
    },
    {
      "question": "food",
      "answer": "food"
    },
    {
      "question": "fool",
      "answer": "fool"
    },
    {
      "question": "foot",
      "answer": "foot"
    },
    {
      "question": "fore",
      "answer": "fore"
    },
    {
      "question": "fork",
      "answer": "fork"
    },
    {
      "question": "form",
      "answer": "form"
    },
    {
      "question": "fort",
      "answer": "fort"
    },
    {
      "question": "foul",
      "answer": "foul"
    },
    {
      "question": "four",
      "answer": "four"
    },
    {
      "question": "fowl",
      "answer": "fowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "fray",
      "answer": "fray"
    },
    {
      "question": "free",
      "answer": "free"
    },
    {
      "question": "fret",
      "answer": "fret"
    },
    {
      "question": "frog",
      "answer": "frog"
    },
    {
      "question": "from",
      "answer": "from"
    },
    {
      "question": "fuel",
      "answer": "fuel"
    },
    {
      "question": "full",
      "answer": "full"
    },
    {
      "question": "fume",
      "answer": "fume"
    },
    {
      "question": "fund",
      "answer": "fund"
    },
    {
      "question": "funk",
      "answer": "funk"
    },
    {
      "question": "fury",
      "answer": "fury"
    },
    {
      "question": "fuse",
      "answer": "fuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "fuss",
      "answer": "fuss"
    },
    {
      "question": "gain",
      "answer": "gain"
    },
    {
      "question": "gala",
      "answer": "gala"
    },
    {
      "question": "gall",
      "answer": "gall"
    },
    {
      "question": "game",
      "answer": "game"
    },
    {
      "question": "gang",
      "answer": "gang"
    },
    {
      "question": "gaol",
      "answer": "gaol"
    },
    {
      "question": "gape",
      "answer": "gape"
    },
    {
      "question": "garb",
      "answer": "garb"
    },
    {
      "question": "gasp",
      "answer": "gasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "gate",
      "answer": "gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "gaze",
      "answer": "gaze"
    },
    {
      "question": "gear",
      "answer": "gear"
    },
    {
      "question": "gene",
      "answer": "gene"
    },
    {
      "question": "germ",
      "answer": "germ"
    },
    {
      "question": "gift",
      "answer": "gift"
    },
    {
      "question": "gild",
      "answer": "gild"
    },
    {
      "question": "gill",
      "answer": "gill"
    },
    {
      "question": "gilt",
      "answer": "gilt"
    },
    {
      "question": "gird",
      "answer": "gird"
    },
    {
      "question": "girl",
      "answer": "girl"
    },
    {
      "question": "give",
      "answer": "give"
    },
    {
      "question": "glad",
      "answer": "glad"
    },
    {
      "question": "glee",
      "answer": "glee"
    },
    {
      "question": "glib",
      "answer": "glib"
    },
    {
      "question": "glow",
      "answer": "glow"
    },
    {
      "question": "glue",
      "answer": "glue"
    },
    {
      "question": "glum",
      "answer": "glum"
    },
    {
      "question": "glut",
      "answer": "glut"
    },
    {
      "question": "gnaw",
      "answer": "gnaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "goad",
      "answer": "goad"
    },
    {
      "question": "goal",
      "answer": "goal"
    },
    {
      "question": "goat",
      "answer": "goat"
    },
    {
      "question": "gold",
      "answer": "gold"
    },
    {
      "question": "golf",
      "answer": "golf"
    },
    {
      "question": "gone",
      "answer": "gone"
    },
    {
      "question": "good",
      "answer": "good"
    },
    {
      "question": "gory",
      "answer": "gory"
    },
    {
      "question": "gown",
      "answer": "gown"
    },
    {
      "question": "grab",
      "answer": "grab"
    },
    {
      "question": "gram",
      "answer": "gram"
    },
    {
      "question": "gray",
      "answer": "gray"
    },
    {
      "question": "grid",
      "answer": "grid"
    },
    {
      "question": "grim",
      "answer": "grim"
    },
    {
      "question": "grin",
      "answer": "grin"
    },
    {
      "question": "grip",
      "answer": "grip"
    },
    {
      "question": "grit",
      "answer": "grit"
    },
    {
      "question": "grow",
      "answer": "grow"
    },
    {
      "question": "gulf",
      "answer": "gulf"
    },
    {
      "question": "gull",
      "answer": "gull"
    },
    {
      "question": "gulp",
      "answer": "gulp"
    },
    {
      "question": "gust",
      "answer": "gust"
    },
    {
      "question": "hack",
      "answer": "hack"
    },
    {
      "question": "hail",
      "answer": "hail"
    },
    {
      "question": "hair",
      "answer": "hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "hale",
      "answer": "hale"
    },
    {
      "question": "half",
      "answer": "half"
    },
    {
      "question": "hall",
      "answer": "hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "halo",
      "answer": "halo"
    },
    {
      "question": "halt",
      "answer": "halt"
    },
    {
      "question": "hand",
      "answer": "hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "hang",
      "answer": "hang"
    },
    {
      "question": "hard",
      "answer": "hard"
    },
    {
      "question": "hare",
      "answer": "hare"
    },
    {
      "question": "hark",
      "answer": "hark"
    },
    {
      "question": "harm",
      "answer": "harm"
    },
    {
      "question": "harp",
      "answer": "harp"
    },
    {
      "question": "hate",
      "answer": "hate"
    },
    {
      "question": "haul",
      "answer": "haul"
    },
    {
      "question": "have",
      "answer": "have"
    },
    {
      "question": "hawk",
      "answer": "hawk"
    },
    {
      "question": "haze",
      "answer": "haze"
    },
    {
      "question": "hazy",
      "answer": "hazy"
    },
    {
      "question": "head",
      "answer": "head"
    },
    {
      "question": "heal",
      "answer": "heal"
    },
    {
      "question": "heap",
      "answer": "heap"
    },
    {
      "question": "hear",
      "answer": "hear"
    },
    {
      "question": "heat",
      "answer": "heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "heed",
      "answer": "heed"
    },
    {
      "question": "heel",
      "answer": "heel"
    },
    {
      "question": "heir",
      "answer": "heir"
    },
    {
      "question": "hell",
      "answer": "hell"
    },
    {
      "question": "helm",
      "answer": "helm"
    },
    {
      "question": "help",
      "answer": "help"
    },
    {
      "question": "herb",
      "answer": "herb"
    },
    {
      "question": "herd",
      "answer": "herd"
    },
    {
      "question": "here",
      "answer": "here"
    },
    {
      "question": "hero",
      "answer": "hero"
    },
    {
      "question": "hers",
      "answer": "hers"
    },
    {
      "question": "hide",
      "answer": "hide"
    },
    {
      "question": "high",
      "answer": "high"
    },
    {
      "question": "hike",
      "answer": "hike"
    },
    {
      "question": "hill",
      "answer": "hill"
    },
    {
      "question": "hind",
      "answer": "hind"
    },
    {
      "question": "hint",
      "answer": "hint"
    },
    {
      "question": "hire",
      "answer": "hire"
    },
    {
      "question": "hiss",
      "answer": "hiss"
    },
    {
      "question": "hive",
      "answer": "hive"
    },
    {
      "question": "hoax",
      "answer": "hoax"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold",
      "answer": "hold"
    },
    {
      "question": "hole",
      "answer": "hole"
    },
    {
      "question": "holy",
      "answer": "holy"
    },
    {
      "question": "home",
      "answer": "home"
    },
    {
      "question": "hone",
      "answer": "hone"
    },
    {
      "question": "honk",
      "answer": "honk"
    },
    {
      "question": "hood",
      "answer": "hood"
    },
    {
      "question": "hoof",
      "answer": "hoof"
    },
    {
      "question": "hook",
      "answer": "hook"
    },
    {
      "question": "hoot",
      "answer": "hoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "hope",
      "answer": "hope"
    },
    {
      "question": "horn",
      "answer": "horn"
    },
    {
      "question": "hose",
      "answer": "hose"
    },
    {
      "question": "host",
      "answer": "host"
    },
    {
      "question": "hour",
      "answer": "hour"
    },
    {
      "question": "howl",
      "answer": "howl"
    },
    {
      "question": "huge",
      "answer": "huge"
    },
    {
      "question": "hula",
      "answer": "hula"
    },
    {
      "question": "hulk",
      "answer": "hulk"
    },
    {
      "question": "hull",
      "answer": "hull"
    },
    {
      "question": "hump",
      "answer": "hump"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunt",
      "answer": "hunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "hurl",
      "answer": "hurl"
    },
    {
      "question": "hurt",
      "answer": "hurt"
    },
    {
      "question": "hush",
      "answer": "hush"
    },
    {
      "question": "husk",
      "answer": "husk"
    },
    {
      "question": "hymn",
      "answer": "hymn"
    },
    {
      "question": "hype",
      "answer": "hype"
    },
    {
      "question": "icon",
      "answer": "icon"
    },
    {
      "question": "idea",
      "answer": "idea"
    },
    {
      "question": "idem",
      "answer": "idem"
    },
    {
      "question": "ides",
      "answer": "ides"
    },
    {
      "question": "idle",
      "answer": "idle"
    },
    {
      "question": "idly",
      "answer": "idly"
    },
    {
      "question": "idol",
      "answer": "idol"
    },
    {
      "question": "inch",
      "answer": "inch"
    },
    {
      "question": "into",
      "answer": "into"
    },
    {
      "question": "iris",
      "answer": "iris"
    },
    {
      "question": "iron",
      "answer": "iron"
    },
    {
      "question": "isle",
      "answer": "isle"
    },
    {
      "question": "itch",
      "answer": "itch"
    },
    {
      "question": "item",
      "answer": "item"
    },
    {
      "question": "jack",
      "answer": "jack"
    },
    {
      "question": "jail",
      "answer": "jail"
    },
    {
      "question": "jazz",
      "answer": "jazz"
    },
    {
      "question": "jeep",
      "answer": "jeep"
    },
    {
      "question": "jeer",
      "answer": "jeer"
    },
    {
      "question": "jerk",
      "answer": "jerk"
    },
    {
      "question": "jest",
      "answer": "jest"
    },
    {
      "question": "join",
      "answer": "join"
    },
    {
      "question": "joke",
      "answer": "joke"
    },
    {
      "question": "jolt",
      "answer": "jolt"
    },
    {
      "question": "july",
      "answer": "july"
    },
    {
      "question": "jump",
      "answer": "jump"
    },
    {
      "question": "june",
      "answer": "june"
    },
    {
      "question": "junk",
      "answer": "junk"
    },
    {
      "question": "jury",
      "answer": "jury"
    },
    {
      "question": "just",
      "answer": "just"
    },
    {
      "question": "kale",
      "answer": "kale"
    },
    {
      "question": "keel",
      "answer": "keel"
    },
    {
      "question": "keen",
      "answer": "keen"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep",
      "answer": "keep"
    },
    {
      "question": "kepi",
      "answer": "kepi"
    },
    {
      "question": "kick",
      "answer": "kick"
    },
    {
      "question": "kill",
      "answer": "kill"
    },
    {
      "question": "kiln",
      "answer": "kiln"
    },
    {
      "question": "kilo",
      "answer": "kilo"
    },
    {
      "question": "kind",
      "answer": "kind"
    },
    {
      "question": "king",
      "answer": "king"
    },
    {
      "question": "kiss",
      "answer": "kiss"
    },
    {
      "question": "kite",
      "answer": "kite"
    },
    {
      "question": "kiwi",
      "answer": "kiwi"
    },
    {
      "question": "knee",
      "answer": "knee"
    },
    {
      "question": "knit",
      "answer": "knit"
    },
    {
      "question": "knob",
      "answer": "knob"
    },
    {
      "question": "knot",
      "answer": "knot"
    },
    {
      "question": "know",
      "answer": "know"
    },
    {
      "question": "lace",
      "answer": "lace"
    },
    {
      "question": "lack",
      "answer": "lack"
    },
    {
      "question": "lady",
      "answer": "lady"
    },
    {
      "question": "laid",
      "answer": "laid"
    },
    {
      "question": "lain",
      "answer": "lain"
    },
    {
      "question": "lair",
      "answer": "lair"
    },
    {
      "question": "lake",
      "answer": "lake"
    },
    {
      "question": "lama",
      "answer": "lama"
    },
    {
      "question": "lamb",
      "answer": "lamb"
    },
    {
      "question": "lame",
      "answer": "lame"
    },
    {
      "question": "lamp",
      "answer": "lamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "land",
      "answer": "land"
    },
    {
      "question": "lane",
      "answer": "lane"
    },
    {
      "question": "lark",
      "answer": "lark"
    },
    {
      "question": "lash",
      "answer": "lash"
    },
    {
      "question": "last",
      "answer": "last"
    },
    {
      "question": "late",
      "answer": "late"
    },
    {
      "question": "lath",
      "answer": "lath"
    },
    {
      "question": "laud",
      "answer": "laud"
    },
    {
      "question": "lava",
      "answer": "lava"
    },
    {
      "question": "lave",
      "answer": "lave"
    },
    {
      "question": "lawn",
      "answer": "lawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "laze",
      "answer": "laze"
    },
    {
      "question": "lazy",
      "answer": "lazy"
    },
    {
      "question": "lead",
      "answer": "lead"
    },
    {
      "question": "leaf",
      "answer": "leaf"
    },
    {
      "question": "leak",
      "answer": "leak"
    },
    {
      "question": "lean",
      "answer": "lean"
    },
    {
      "question": "leap",
      "answer": "leap"
    },
    {
      "question": "leek",
      "answer": "leek"
    },
    {
      "question": "leer",
      "answer": "leer"
    },
    {
      "question": "lees",
      "answer": "lees"
    },
    {
      "question": "left",
      "answer": "left"
    },
    {
      "question": "lend",
      "answer": "lend"
    },
    {
      "question": "lens",
      "answer": "lens"
    },
    {
      "question": "less",
      "answer": "less"
    },
    {
      "question": "lest",
      "answer": "lest"
    },
    {
      "question": "levy",
      "answer": "levy"
    },
    {
      "question": "lewd",
      "answer": "lewd"
    },
    {
      "question": "liar",
      "answer": "liar"
    },
    {
      "question": "lick",
      "answer": "lick"
    },
    {
      "question": "lido",
      "answer": "lido"
    },
    {
      "question": "lied",
      "answer": "lied"
    },
    {
      "question": "lief",
      "answer": "lief"
    },
    {
      "question": "lien",
      "answer": "lien"
    },
    {
      "question": "life",
      "answer": "life"
    },
    {
      "question": "lift",
      "answer": "lift"
    },
    {
      "question": "like",
      "answer": "like"
    },
    {
      "question": "lilt",
      "answer": "lilt"
    },
    {
      "question": "lily",
      "answer": "lily"
    },
    {
      "question": "limb",
      "answer": "limb"
    },
    {
      "question": "lime",
      "answer": "lime"
    },
    {
      "question": "limp",
      "answer": "limp"
    },
    {
      "question": "line",
      "answer": "line"
    },
    {
      "question": "link",
      "answer": "link"
    },
    {
      "question": "lion",
      "answer": "lion"
    },
    {
      "question": "lira",
      "answer": "lira"
    },
    {
      "question": "lisp",
      "answer": "lisp"
    },
    {
      "question": "list",
      "answer": "list"
    },
    {
      "question": "live",
      "answer": "live"
    },
    {
      "question": "load",
      "answer": "load"
    },
    {
      "question": "loaf",
      "answer": "loaf"
    },
    {
      "question": "loan",
      "answer": "loan"
    },
    {
      "question": "lobe",
      "answer": "lobe"
    },
    {
      "question": "lock",
      "answer": "lock"
    },
    {
      "question": "loft",
      "answer": "loft"
    },
    {
      "question": "logo",
      "answer": "logo"
    },
    {
      "question": "loin",
      "answer": "loin"
    },
    {
      "question": "lone",
      "answer": "lone"
    },
    {
      "question": "long",
      "answer": "long"
    },
    {
      "question": "look",
      "answer": "look"
    },
    {
      "question": "loom",
      "answer": "loom"
    },
    {
      "question": "loop",
      "answer": "loop"
    },
    {
      "question": "loot",
      "answer": "loot"
    },
    {
      "question": "lope",
      "answer": "lope"
    },
    {
      "question": "lord",
      "answer": "lord"
    },
    {
      "question": "lore",
      "answer": "lore"
    },
    {
      "question": "lose",
      "answer": "lose"
    },
    {
      "question": "loss",
      "answer": "loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "lost",
      "answer": "lost"
    },
    {
      "question": "loud",
      "answer": "loud"
    },
    {
      "question": "love",
      "answer": "love"
    },
    {
      "question": "luck",
      "answer": "luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "lull",
      "answer": "lull"
    },
    {
      "question": "lump",
      "answer": "lump"
    },
    {
      "question": "lung",
      "answer": "lung"
    },
    {
      "question": "lure",
      "answer": "lure"
    },
    {
      "question": "lush",
      "answer": "lush"
    },
    {
      "question": "lynx",
      "answer": "lynx"
    },
    {
      "question": "lyre",
      "answer": "lyre"
    },
    {
      "question": "maid",
      "answer": "maid"
    },
    {
      "question": "mail",
      "answer": "mail"
    },
    {
      "question": "main",
      "answer": "main"
    },
    {
      "question": "make",
      "answer": "make"
    },
    {
      "question": "male",
      "answer": "male"
    },
    {
      "question": "malt",
      "answer": "malt"
    },
    {
      "question": "mama",
      "answer": "mama"
    },
    {
      "question": "mane",
      "answer": "mane"
    },
    {
      "question": "many",
      "answer": "many"
    },
    {
      "question": "mare",
      "answer": "mare"
    },
    {
      "question": "mark",
      "answer": "mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "mart",
      "answer": "mart"
    },
    {
      "question": "mash",
      "answer": "mash"
    },
    {
      "question": "mask",
      "answer": "mask"
    },
    {
      "question": "mass",
      "answer": "mass"
    },
    {
      "question": "mast",
      "answer": "mast"
    },
    {
      "question": "mate",
      "answer": "mate"
    },
    {
      "question": "meal",
      "answer": "meal"
    },
    {
      "question": "mean",
      "answer": "mean"
    },
    {
      "question": "meat",
      "answer": "meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "meed",
      "answer": "meed"
    },
    {
      "question": "meek",
      "answer": "meek"
    },
    {
      "question": "meet",
      "answer": "meet"
    },
    {
      "question": "melt",
      "answer": "melt"
    },
    {
      "question": "memo",
      "answer": "memo"
    },
    {
      "question": "mend",
      "answer": "mend"
    },
    {
      "question": "menu",
      "answer": "menu"
    },
    {
      "question": "mere",
      "answer": "mere"
    },
    {
      "question": "mesa",
      "answer": "mesa"
    },
    {
      "question": "mess",
      "answer": "mess"
    },
    {
      "question": "mete",
      "answer": "mete"
    },
    {
      "question": "mien",
      "answer": "mien"
    },
    {
      "question": "mild",
      "answer": "mild"
    },
    {
      "question": "mile",
      "answer": "mile"
    },
    {
      "question": "milk",
      "answer": "milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "mill",
      "answer": "mill"
    },
    {
      "question": "mind",
      "answer": "mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "mine",
      "answer": "mine"
    },
    {
      "question": "mini",
      "answer": "mini"
    },
    {
      "question": "miss",
      "answer": "miss"
    },
    {
      "question": "mist",
      "answer": "mist"
    },
    {
      "question": "mite",
      "answer": "mite"
    },
    {
      "question": "moan",
      "answer": "moan"
    },
    {
      "question": "moat",
      "answer": "moat"
    },
    {
      "question": "mock",
      "answer": "mock"
    },
    {
      "question": "mode",
      "answer": "mode"
    },
    {
      "question": "mold",
      "answer": "mold"
    },
    {
      "question": "mole",
      "answer": "mole"
    },
    {
      "question": "monk",
      "answer": "monk"
    },
    {
      "question": "mood",
      "answer": "mood"
    },
    {
      "question": "moon",
      "answer": "moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "moor",
      "answer": "moor"
    },
    {
      "question": "moot",
      "answer": "moot"
    },
    {
      "question": "mope",
      "answer": "mope"
    },
    {
      "question": "more",
      "answer": "more"
    },
    {
      "question": "morn",
      "answer": "morn"
    },
    {
      "question": "moss",
      "answer": "moss"
    },
    {
      "question": "most",
      "answer": "most"
    },
    {
      "question": "mote",
      "answer": "mote"
    },
    {
      "question": "move",
      "answer": "move"
    },
    {
      "question": "much",
      "answer": "much"
    },
    {
      "question": "muck",
      "answer": "muck"
    },
    {
      "question": "mule",
      "answer": "mule"
    },
    {
      "question": "mull",
      "answer": "mull"
    },
    {
      "question": "muse",
      "answer": "muse"
    },
    {
      "question": "must",
      "answer": "must"
    },
    {
      "question": "mute",
      "answer": "mute"
    },
    {
      "question": "myna",
      "answer": "myna"
    },
    {
      "question": "myth",
      "answer": "myth"
    },
    {
      "question": "nail",
      "answer": "nail"
    },
    {
      "question": "name",
      "answer": "name"
    },
    {
      "question": "nape",
      "answer": "nape"
    },
    {
      "question": "nard",
      "answer": "nard"
    },
    {
      "question": "nave",
      "answer": "nave"
    },
    {
      "question": "navy",
      "answer": "navy"
    },
    {
      "question": "neap",
      "answer": "neap"
    },
    {
      "question": "near",
      "answer": "near"
    },
    {
      "question": "neat",
      "answer": "neat"
    },
    {
      "question": "neck",
      "answer": "neck"
    },
    {
      "question": "need",
      "answer": "need"
    },
    {
      "question": "neon",
      "answer": "neon"
    },
    {
      "question": "nest",
      "answer": "nest"
    },
    {
      "question": "news",
      "answer": "news"
    },
    {
      "question": "next",
      "answer": "next"
    },
    {
      "question": "nice",
      "answer": "nice"
    },
    {
      "question": "nick",
      "answer": "nick"
    },
    {
      "question": "nine",
      "answer": "nine"
    },
    {
      "question": "node",
      "answer": "node"
    },
    {
      "question": "noel",
      "answer": "noel"
    },
    {
      "question": "none",
      "answer": "none"
    },
    {
      "question": "nook",
      "answer": "nook"
    },
    {
      "question": "noon",
      "answer": "noon"
    },
    {
      "question": "norm",
      "answer": "norm"
    },
    {
      "question": "nose",
      "answer": "nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "note",
      "answer": "note"
    },
    {
      "question": "noun",
      "answer": "noun"
    },
    {
      "question": "null",
      "answer": "null"
    },
    {
      "question": "numb",
      "answer": "numb"
    },
    {
      "question": "nuts",
      "answer": "nuts"
    },
    {
      "question": "oath",
      "answer": "oath"
    },
    {
      "question": "obey",
      "answer": "obey"
    },
    {
      "question": "odor",
      "answer": "odor"
    },
    {
      "question": "oily",
      "answer": "oily"
    },
    {
      "question": "omen",
      "answer": "omen"
    },
    {
      "question": "omit",
      "answer": "omit"
    },
    {
      "question": "once",
      "answer": "once"
    },
    {
      "question": "only",
      "answer": "only"
    },
    {
      "question": "onto",
      "answer": "onto"
    },
    {
      "question": "onus",
      "answer": "onus"
    },
    {
      "question": "ooze",
      "answer": "ooze"
    },
    {
      "question": "open",
      "answer": "open"
    },
    {
      "question": "opus",
      "answer": "opus"
    },
    {
      "question": "oral",
      "answer": "oral"
    },
    {
      "question": "ours",
      "answer": "ours"
    },
    {
      "question": "oust",
      "answer": "oust"
    },
    {
      "question": "oval",
      "answer": "oval"
    },
    {
      "question": "oven",
      "answer": "oven"
    },
    {
      "question": "over",
      "answer": "over"
    },
    {
      "question": "pace",
      "answer": "pace"
    },
    {
      "question": "pack",
      "answer": "pack"
    },
    {
      "question": "pact",
      "answer": "pact"
    },
    {
      "question": "page",
      "answer": "page"
    },
    {
      "question": "paid",
      "answer": "paid"
    },
    {
      "question": "pail",
      "answer": "pail"
    },
    {
      "question": "pain",
      "answer": "pain"
    },
    {
      "question": "pair",
      "answer": "pair"
    },
    {
      "question": "pale",
      "answer": "pale"
    },
    {
      "question": "pall",
      "answer": "pall"
    },
    {
      "question": "palm",
      "answer": "palm"
    },
    {
      "question": "pane",
      "answer": "pane"
    },
    {
      "question": "pang",
      "answer": "pang"
    },
    {
      "question": "pant",
      "answer": "pant"
    },
    {
      "question": "papa",
      "answer": "papa"
    },
    {
      "question": "pare",
      "answer": "pare"
    },
    {
      "question": "park",
      "answer": "park"
    },
    {
      "question": "part",
      "answer": "part"
    },
    {
      "question": "pass",
      "answer": "pass"
    },
    {
      "question": "past",
      "answer": "past"
    },
    {
      "question": "pate",
      "answer": "pate"
    },
    {
      "question": "path",
      "answer": "path"
    },
    {
      "question": "pave",
      "answer": "pave"
    },
    {
      "question": "pawn",
      "answer": "pawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "peak",
      "answer": "peak"
    },
    {
      "question": "peal",
      "answer": "peal"
    },
    {
      "question": "pear",
      "answer": "pear"
    },
    {
      "question": "peat",
      "answer": "peat"
    },
    {
      "question": "peck",
      "answer": "peck"
    },
    {
      "question": "peek",
      "answer": "peek"
    },
    {
      "question": "peel",
      "answer": "peel"
    },
    {
      "question": "peep",
      "answer": "peep"
    },
    {
      "question": "peer",
      "answer": "peer"
    },
    {
      "question": "pelt",
      "answer": "pelt"
    },
    {
      "question": "peon",
      "answer": "peon"
    },
    {
      "question": "perk",
      "answer": "perk"
    },
    {
      "question": "pert",
      "answer": "pert"
    },
    {
      "question": "peso",
      "answer": "peso"
    },
    {
      "question": "pest",
      "answer": "pest"
    },
    {
      "question": "pice",
      "answer": "pice"
    },
    {
      "question": "pick",
      "answer": "pick"
    },
    {
      "question": "pier",
      "answer": "pier"
    },
    {
      "question": "pike",
      "answer": "pike"
    },
    {
      "question": "pile",
      "answer": "pile"
    },
    {
      "question": "pill",
      "answer": "pill"
    },
    {
      "question": "pimp",
      "answer": "pimp"
    },
    {
      "question": "pine",
      "answer": "pine"
    },
    {
      "question": "pink",
      "answer": "pink"
    },
    {
      "question": "pint",
      "answer": "pint"
    },
    {
      "question": "pipe",
      "answer": "pipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "piss",
      "answer": "piss"
    },
    {
      "question": "pity",
      "answer": "pity"
    },
    {
      "question": "plan",
      "answer": "plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "play",
      "answer": "play"
    },
    {
      "question": "plea",
      "answer": "plea"
    },
    {
      "question": "plod",
      "answer": "plod"
    },
    {
      "question": "plot",
      "answer": "plot"
    },
    {
      "question": "plow",
      "answer": "plow"
    },
    {
      "question": "plug",
      "answer": "plug"
    },
    {
      "question": "plum",
      "answer": "plum"
    },
    {
      "question": "plus",
      "answer": "plus"
    },
    {
      "question": "poem",
      "answer": "poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "poet",
      "answer": "poet"
    },
    {
      "question": "poke",
      "answer": "poke"
    },
    {
      "question": "pole",
      "answer": "pole"
    },
    {
      "question": "poll",
      "answer": "poll"
    },
    {
      "question": "polo",
      "answer": "polo"
    },
    {
      "question": "pomp",
      "answer": "pomp"
    },
    {
      "question": "pond",
      "answer": "pond"
    },
    {
      "question": "pone",
      "answer": "pone"
    },
    {
      "question": "pony",
      "answer": "pony"
    },
    {
      "question": "pool",
      "answer": "pool"
    },
    {
      "question": "poor",
      "answer": "poor"
    },
    {
      "question": "pope",
      "answer": "pope"
    },
    {
      "question": "pore",
      "answer": "pore"
    },
    {
      "question": "pork",
      "answer": "pork"
    },
    {
      "question": "port",
      "answer": "port"
    },
    {
      "question": "pose",
      "answer": "pose"
    },
    {
      "question": "posh",
      "answer": "posh"
    },
    {
      "question": "post",
      "answer": "post"
    },
    {
      "question": "pour",
      "answer": "pour"
    },
    {
      "question": "pout",
      "answer": "pout"
    },
    {
      "question": "pram",
      "answer": "pram"
    },
    {
      "question": "pray",
      "answer": "pray"
    },
    {
      "question": "prey",
      "answer": "prey"
    },
    {
      "question": "prig",
      "answer": "prig"
    },
    {
      "question": "prim",
      "answer": "prim"
    },
    {
      "question": "prod",
      "answer": "prod"
    },
    {
      "question": "prom",
      "answer": "prom"
    },
    {
      "question": "prop",
      "answer": "prop"
    },
    {
      "question": "puff",
      "answer": "puff"
    },
    {
      "question": "pull",
      "answer": "pull"
    },
    {
      "question": "pulp",
      "answer": "pulp"
    },
    {
      "question": "pump",
      "answer": "pump"
    },
    {
      "question": "punk",
      "answer": "punk"
    },
    {
      "question": "pure",
      "answer": "pure"
    },
    {
      "question": "purr",
      "answer": "purr"
    },
    {
      "question": "push",
      "answer": "push"
    },
    {
      "question": "putt",
      "answer": "putt"
    },
    {
      "question": "pyre",
      "answer": "pyre"
    },
    {
      "question": "quay",
      "answer": "quay"
    },
    {
      "question": "quid",
      "answer": "quid"
    },
    {
      "question": "quip",
      "answer": "quip"
    },
    {
      "question": "quit",
      "answer": "quit"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiz",
      "answer": "quiz"
    },
    {
      "question": "race",
      "answer": "race"
    },
    {
      "question": "rack",
      "answer": "rack"
    },
    {
      "question": "rage",
      "answer": "rage"
    },
    {
      "question": "raid",
      "answer": "raid"
    },
    {
      "question": "rail",
      "answer": "rail"
    },
    {
      "question": "rain",
      "answer": "rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "rake",
      "answer": "rake"
    },
    {
      "question": "ramp",
      "answer": "ramp"
    },
    {
      "question": "rand",
      "answer": "rand"
    },
    {
      "question": "rani",
      "answer": "rani"
    },
    {
      "question": "rank",
      "answer": "rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "rant",
      "answer": "rant"
    },
    {
      "question": "rapt",
      "answer": "rapt"
    },
    {
      "question": "rare",
      "answer": "rare"
    },
    {
      "question": "rash",
      "answer": "rash"
    },
    {
      "question": "rasp",
      "answer": "rasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "rate",
      "answer": "rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "raze",
      "answer": "raze"
    },
    {
      "question": "read",
      "answer": "read"
    },
    {
      "question": "real",
      "answer": "real"
    },
    {
      "question": "ream",
      "answer": "ream"
    },
    {
      "question": "reap",
      "answer": "reap"
    },
    {
      "question": "rear",
      "answer": "rear"
    },
    {
      "question": "reed",
      "answer": "reed"
    },
    {
      "question": "reef",
      "answer": "reef"
    },
    {
      "question": "reel",
      "answer": "reel"
    },
    {
      "question": "rein",
      "answer": "rein"
    },
    {
      "question": "rely",
      "answer": "rely"
    },
    {
      "question": "rent",
      "answer": "rent"
    },
    {
      "question": "rest",
      "answer": "rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "rial",
      "answer": "rial"
    },
    {
      "question": "rice",
      "answer": "rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "rich",
      "answer": "rich"
    },
    {
      "question": "ride",
      "answer": "ride"
    },
    {
      "question": "rife",
      "answer": "rife"
    },
    {
      "question": "rift",
      "answer": "rift"
    },
    {
      "question": "rind",
      "answer": "rind"
    },
    {
      "question": "ring",
      "answer": "ring"
    },
    {
      "question": "rink",
      "answer": "rink"
    },
    {
      "question": "riot",
      "answer": "riot"
    },
    {
      "question": "ripe",
      "answer": "ripe"
    },
    {
      "question": "rise",
      "answer": "rise"
    },
    {
      "question": "risk",
      "answer": "risk"
    },
    {
      "question": "rite",
      "answer": "rite"
    },
    {
      "question": "road",
      "answer": "road"
    },
    {
      "question": "roam",
      "answer": "roam"
    },
    {
      "question": "roar",
      "answer": "roar"
    },
    {
      "question": "robe",
      "answer": "robe"
    },
    {
      "question": "rock",
      "answer": "rock"
    },
    {
      "question": "role",
      "answer": "role"
    },
    {
      "question": "roll",
      "answer": "roll"
    },
    {
      "question": "romp",
      "answer": "romp"
    },
    {
      "question": "rood",
      "answer": "rood"
    },
    {
      "question": "roof",
      "answer": "roof"
    },
    {
      "question": "room",
      "answer": "room"
    },
    {
      "question": "root",
      "answer": "root"
    },
    {
      "question": "rope",
      "answer": "rope"
    },
    {
      "question": "rose",
      "answer": "rose"
    },
    {
      "question": "rosy",
      "answer": "rosy"
    },
    {
      "question": "rout",
      "answer": "rout"
    },
    {
      "question": "rove",
      "answer": "rove"
    },
    {
      "question": "ruby",
      "answer": "ruby"
    },
    {
      "question": "rude",
      "answer": "rude"
    },
    {
      "question": "ruin",
      "answer": "ruin"
    },
    {
      "question": "rule",
      "answer": "rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "rump",
      "answer": "rump"
    },
    {
      "question": "rung",
      "answer": "rung"
    },
    {
      "question": "runt",
      "answer": "runt"
    },
    {
      "question": "ruse",
      "answer": "ruse"
    },
    {
      "question": "rush",
      "answer": "rush"
    },
    {
      "question": "rust",
      "answer": "rust"
    },
    {
      "question": "sack",
      "answer": "sack"
    },
    {
      "question": "safe",
      "answer": "safe"
    },
    {
      "question": "saga",
      "answer": "saga"
    },
    {
      "question": "sage",
      "answer": "sage"
    },
    {
      "question": "sail",
      "answer": "sail"
    },
    {
      "question": "sake",
      "answer": "sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "sale",
      "answer": "sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "salt",
      "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
      "question": "same",
      "answer": "same"
    },
    {
      "question": "sand",
      "answer": "sand"
    },
    {
      "question": "sane",
      "answer": "sane"
    },
    {
      "question": "sang",
      "answer": "sang"
    },
    {
      "question": "sate",
      "answer": "sate"
    },
    {
      "question": "save",
      "answer": "save"
    },
    {
      "question": "scar",
      "answer": "scar"
    },
    {
      "question": "scum",
      "answer": "scum"
    },
    {
      "question": "seal",
      "answer": "seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "seam",
      "answer": "seam"
    },
    {
      "question": "sear",
      "answer": "sear"
    },
    {
      "question": "seat",
      "answer": "seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "sect",
      "answer": "sect"
    },
    {
      "question": "seed",
      "answer": "seed"
    },
    {
      "question": "seek",
      "answer": "seek"
    },
    {
      "question": "seem",
      "answer": "seem"
    },
    {
      "question": "seep",
      "answer": "seep"
    },
    {
      "question": "self",
      "answer": "self"
    },
    {
      "question": "sell",
      "answer": "sell"
    },
    {
      "question": "send",
      "answer": "send"
    },
    {
      "question": "sent",
      "answer": "sent"
    },
    {
      "question": "sera",
      "answer": "sera"
    },
    {
      "question": "shad",
      "answer": "shad"
    },
    {
      "question": "sham",
      "answer": "sham"
    },
    {
      "question": "shed",
      "answer": "shed"
    },
    {
      "question": "shin",
      "answer": "shin"
    },
    {
      "question": "ship",
      "answer": "ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "shoe",
      "answer": "shoe"
    },
    {
      "question": "shop",
      "answer": "shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "shot",
      "answer": "shot"
    },
    {
      "question": "show",
      "answer": "show"
    },
    {
      "question": "shun",
      "answer": "shun"
    },
    {
      "question": "shut",
      "answer": "shut"
    },
    {
      "question": "sick",
      "answer": "sick"
    },
    {
      "question": "side",
      "answer": "side"
    },
    {
      "question": "sift",
      "answer": "sift"
    },
    {
      "question": "sigh",
      "answer": "sigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "sign",
      "answer": "sign"
    },
    {
      "question": "silk",
      "answer": "silk"
    },
    {
      "question": "silo",
      "answer": "silo"
    },
    {
      "question": "silt",
      "answer": "silt"
    },
    {
      "question": "sing",
      "answer": "sing"
    },
    {
      "question": "sink",
      "answer": "sink"
    },
    {
      "question": "sire",
      "answer": "sire"
    },
    {
      "question": "site",
      "answer": "site"
    },
    {
      "question": "size",
      "answer": "size"
    },
    {
      "question": "skid",
      "answer": "skid"
    },
    {
      "question": "skim",
      "answer": "skim"
    },
    {
      "question": "skin",
      "answer": "skin"
    },
    {
      "question": "skip",
      "answer": "skip"
    },
    {
      "question": "slab",
      "answer": "slab"
    },
    {
      "question": "slam",
      "answer": "slam"
    },
    {
      "question": "slap",
      "answer": "slap"
    },
    {
      "question": "slat",
      "answer": "slat"
    },
    {
      "question": "slay",
      "answer": "slay"
    },
    {
      "question": "sled",
      "answer": "sled"
    },
    {
      "question": "slim",
      "answer": "slim"
    },
    {
      "question": "slip",
      "answer": "slip"
    },
    {
      "question": "slit",
      "answer": "slit"
    },
    {
      "question": "sloe",
      "answer": "sloe"
    },
    {
      "question": "slot",
      "answer": "slot"
    },
    {
      "question": "slow",
      "answer": "slow"
    },
    {
      "question": "slug",
      "answer": "slug"
    },
    {
      "question": "slur",
      "answer": "slur"
    },
    {
      "question": "smog",
      "answer": "smog"
    },
    {
      "question": "smug",
      "answer": "smug"
    },
    {
      "question": "snag",
      "answer": "snag"
    },
    {
      "question": "snap",
      "answer": "snap"
    },
    {
      "question": "snip",
      "answer": "snip"
    },
    {
      "question": "snob",
      "answer": "snob"
    },
    {
      "question": "snow",
      "answer": "snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "snub",
      "answer": "snub"
    },
    {
      "question": "snug",
      "answer": "snug"
    },
    {
      "question": "soak",
      "answer": "soak"
    },
    {
      "question": "soap",
      "answer": "soap"
    },
    {
      "question": "soar",
      "answer": "soar"
    },
    {
      "question": "sock",
      "answer": "sock"
    },
    {
      "question": "soda",
      "answer": "soda"
    },
    {
      "question": "sofa",
      "answer": "sofa"
    },
    {
      "question": "soft",
      "answer": "soft"
    },
    {
      "question": "soil",
      "answer": "soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "sole",
      "answer": "sole"
    },
    {
      "question": "solo",
      "answer": "solo"
    },
    {
      "question": "some",
      "answer": "some"
    },
    {
      "question": "song",
      "answer": "song"
    },
    {
      "question": "soon",
      "answer": "soon"
    },
    {
      "question": "soot",
      "answer": "soot"
    },
    {
      "question": "sore",
      "answer": "sore"
    },
    {
      "question": "sort",
      "answer": "sort"
    },
    {
      "question": "soul",
      "answer": "soul"
    },
    {
      "question": "soup",
      "answer": "soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "sour",
      "answer": "sour"
    },
    {
      "question": "span",
      "answer": "span"
    },
    {
      "question": "spar",
      "answer": "spar"
    },
    {
      "question": "spat",
      "answer": "spat"
    },
    {
      "question": "spin",
      "answer": "spin"
    },
    {
      "question": "spit",
      "answer": "spit"
    },
    {
      "question": "spot",
      "answer": "spot"
    },
    {
      "question": "spur",
      "answer": "spur"
    },
    {
      "question": "stab",
      "answer": "stab"
    },
    {
      "question": "stag",
      "answer": "stag"
    },
    {
      "question": "star",
      "answer": "star"
    },
    {
      "question": "stay",
      "answer": "stay"
    },
    {
      "question": "stem",
      "answer": "stem"
    },
    {
      "question": "step",
      "answer": "step"
    },
    {
      "question": "stew",
      "answer": "stew"
    },
    {
      "question": "stir",
      "answer": "stir"
    },
    {
      "question": "stop",
      "answer": "stop"
    },
    {
      "question": "stow",
      "answer": "stow"
    },
    {
      "question": "stub",
      "answer": "stub"
    },
    {
      "question": "stud",
      "answer": "stud"
    },
    {
      "question": "stun",
      "answer": "stun"
    },
    {
      "question": "such",
      "answer": "such"
    },
    {
      "question": "suit",
      "answer": "suit"
    },
    {
      "question": "sulk",
      "answer": "sulk"
    },
    {
      "question": "sung",
      "answer": "sung"
    },
    {
      "question": "sunk",
      "answer": "sunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "sure",
      "answer": "sure"
    },
    {
      "question": "surf",
      "answer": "surf"
    },
    {
      "question": "swan",
      "answer": "swan"
    },
    {
      "question": "swap",
      "answer": "swap"
    },
    {
      "question": "sway",
      "answer": "sway"
    },
    {
      "question": "swim",
      "answer": "swim"
    },
    {
      "question": "tact",
      "answer": "tact"
    },
    {
      "question": "tail",
      "answer": "tail"
    },
    {
      "question": "take",
      "answer": "take"
    },
    {
      "question": "tale",
      "answer": "tale"
    },
    {
      "question": "talk",
      "answer": "talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "tall",
      "answer": "tall"
    },
    {
      "question": "tame",
      "answer": "tame"
    },
    {
      "question": "tank",
      "answer": "tank"
    },
    {
      "question": "tape",
      "answer": "tape"
    },
    {
      "question": "taps",
      "answer": "taps"
    },
    {
      "question": "tare",
      "answer": "tare"
    },
    {
      "question": "tarn",
      "answer": "tarn"
    },
    {
      "question": "tart",
      "answer": "tart"
    },
    {
      "question": "task",
      "answer": "task"
    },
    {
      "question": "taut",
      "answer": "taut"
    },
    {
      "question": "taxi",
      "answer": "taxi"
    },
    {
      "question": "teak",
      "answer": "teak"
    },
    {
      "question": "teal",
      "answer": "teal"
    },
    {
      "question": "team",
      "answer": "team"
    },
    {
      "question": "tear",
      "answer": "tear"
    },
    {
      "question": "teem",
      "answer": "teem"
    },
    {
      "question": "teen",
      "answer": "teen"
    },
    {
      "question": "tell",
      "answer": "tell"
    },
    {
      "question": "tend",
      "answer": "tend"
    },
    {
      "question": "tent",
      "answer": "tent"
    },
    {
      "question": "term",
      "answer": "term"
    },
    {
      "question": "tern",
      "answer": "tern"
    },
    {
      "question": "test",
      "answer": "test"
    },
    {
      "question": "text",
      "answer": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "than",
      "answer": "than"
    },
    {
      "question": "that",
      "answer": "that"
    },
    {
      "question": "thaw",
      "answer": "thaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "thee",
      "answer": "thee"
    },
    {
      "question": "them",
      "answer": "them"
    },
    {
      "question": "then",
      "answer": "then"
    },
    {
      "question": "thew",
      "answer": "thew"
    },
    {
      "question": "they",
      "answer": "they"
    },
    {
      "question": "thin",
      "answer": "thin"
    },
    {
      "question": "this",
      "answer": "this"
    },
    {
      "question": "thou",
      "answer": "thou"
    },
    {
      "question": "thud",
      "answer": "thud"
    },
    {
      "question": "thug",
      "answer": "thug"
    },
    {
      "question": "thus",
      "answer": "thus"
    },
    {
      "question": "tick",
      "answer": "tick"
    },
    {
      "question": "tide",
      "answer": "tide"
    },
    {
      "question": "tidy",
      "answer": "tidy"
    },
    {
      "question": "tier",
      "answer": "tier"
    },
    {
      "question": "tile",
      "answer": "tile"
    },
    {
      "question": "till",
      "answer": "till"
    },
    {
      "question": "time",
      "answer": "time"
    },
    {
      "question": "tint",
      "answer": "tint"
    },
    {
      "question": "tiny",
      "answer": "tiny"
    },
    {
      "question": "tire",
      "answer": "tire"
    },
    {
      "question": "toad",
      "answer": "toad"
    },
    {
      "question": "toga",
      "answer": "toga"
    },
    {
      "question": "toil",
      "answer": "toil"
    },
    {
      "question": "toll",
      "answer": "toll"
    },
    {
      "question": "tomb",
      "answer": "tomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "tome",
      "answer": "tome"
    },
    {
      "question": "tone",
      "answer": "tone"
    },
    {
      "question": "tool",
      "answer": "tool"
    },
    {
      "question": "tope",
      "answer": "tope"
    },
    {
      "question": "tops",
      "answer": "tops"
    },
    {
      "question": "toss",
      "answer": "toss"
    },
    {
      "question": "tour",
      "answer": "tour"
    },
    {
      "question": "tout",
      "answer": "tout"
    },
    {
      "question": "town",
      "answer": "town"
    },
    {
      "question": "tram",
      "answer": "tram"
    },
    {
      "question": "trap",
      "answer": "trap"
    },
    {
      "question": "tray",
      "answer": "tray"
    },
    {
      "question": "tree",
      "answer": "tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "trek",
      "answer": "trek"
    },
    {
      "question": "trig",
      "answer": "trig"
    },
    {
      "question": "trim",
      "answer": "trim"
    },
    {
      "question": "trio",
      "answer": "trio"
    },
    {
      "question": "trip",
      "answer": "trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "true",
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "question": "tsar",
      "answer": "tsar"
    },
    {
      "question": "tube",
      "answer": "tube"
    },
    {
      "question": "tuck",
      "answer": "tuck"
    },
    {
      "question": "tuna",
      "answer": "tuna"
    },
    {
      "question": "tune",
      "answer": "tune"
    },
    {
      "question": "turf",
      "answer": "turf"
    },
    {
      "question": "turn",
      "answer": "turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "twig",
      "answer": "twig"
    },
    {
      "question": "twin",
      "answer": "twin"
    },
    {
      "question": "type",
      "answer": "type"
    },
    {
      "question": "ugly",
      "answer": "ugly"
    },
    {
      "question": "undo",
      "answer": "undo"
    },
    {
      "question": "unit",
      "answer": "unit"
    },
    {
      "question": "upon",
      "answer": "upon"
    },
    {
      "question": "urge",
      "answer": "urge"
    },
    {
      "question": "used",
      "answer": "used"
    },
    {
      "question": "vain",
      "answer": "vain"
    },
    {
      "question": "vale",
      "answer": "vale"
    },
    {
      "question": "vane",
      "answer": "vane"
    },
    {
      "question": "vary",
      "answer": "vary"
    },
    {
      "question": "vase",
      "answer": "vase"
    },
    {
      "question": "vast",
      "answer": "vast"
    },
    {
      "question": "veal",
      "answer": "veal"
    },
    {
      "question": "veer",
      "answer": "veer"
    },
    {
      "question": "veil",
      "answer": "veil"
    },
    {
      "question": "vein",
      "answer": "vein"
    },
    {
      "question": "verb",
      "answer": "verb"
    },
    {
      "question": "very",
      "answer": "very"
    },
    {
      "question": "vest",
      "answer": "vest"
    },
    {
      "question": "veto",
      "answer": "veto"
    },
    {
      "question": "vice",
      "answer": "vice"
    },
    {
      "question": "vide",
      "answer": "vide"
    },
    {
      "question": "view",
      "answer": "view"
    },
    {
      "question": "vile",
      "answer": "vile"
    },
    {
      "question": "vine",
      "answer": "vine"
    },
    {
      "question": "visa",
      "answer": "visa"
    },
    {
      "question": "void",
      "answer": "void"
    },
    {
      "question": "vole",
      "answer": "vole"
    },
    {
      "question": "vote",
      "answer": "vote"
    },
    {
      "question": "wade",
      "answer": "wade"
    },
    {
      "question": "waft",
      "answer": "waft"
    },
    {
      "question": "wage",
      "answer": "wage"
    },
    {
      "question": "wail",
      "answer": "wail"
    },
    {
      "question": "wait",
      "answer": "wait"
    },
    {
      "question": "wake",
      "answer": "wake"
    },
    {
      "question": "walk",
      "answer": "walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "wall",
      "answer": "wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "wand",
      "answer": "wand"
    },
    {
      "question": "wane",
      "answer": "wane"
    },
    {
      "question": "want",
      "answer": "want"
    },
    {
      "question": "ward",
      "answer": "ward"
    },
    {
      "question": "ware",
      "answer": "ware"
    },
    {
      "question": "warm",
      "answer": "warm"
    },
    {
      "question": "warn",
      "answer": "warn"
    },
    {
      "question": "warp",
      "answer": "warp"
    },
    {
      "question": "wart",
      "answer": "wart"
    },
    {
      "question": "wary",
      "answer": "wary"
    },
    {
      "question": "wash",
      "answer": "wash"
    },
    {
      "question": "wasp",
      "answer": "wasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "watt",
      "answer": "watt"
    },
    {
      "question": "wave",
      "answer": "wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "weak",
      "answer": "weak"
    },
    {
      "question": "wean",
      "answer": "wean"
    },
    {
      "question": "wear",
      "answer": "wear"
    },
    {
      "question": "weed",
      "answer": "weed"
    },
    {
      "question": "week",
      "answer": "week"
    },
    {
      "question": "weep",
      "answer": "weep"
    },
    {
      "question": "weir",
      "answer": "weir"
    },
    {
      "question": "weld",
      "answer": "weld"
    },
    {
      "question": "well",
      "answer": "well"
    },
    {
      "question": "were",
      "answer": "were"
    },
    {
      "question": "west",
      "answer": "west"
    },
    {
      "question": "what",
      "answer": "what"
    },
    {
      "question": "when",
      "answer": "when"
    },
    {
      "question": "whet",
      "answer": "whet"
    },
    {
      "question": "whim",
      "answer": "whim"
    },
    {
      "question": "whip",
      "answer": "whip"
    },
    {
      "question": "whit",
      "answer": "whit"
    },
    {
      "question": "whom",
      "answer": "whom"
    },
    {
      "question": "wide",
      "answer": "wide"
    },
    {
      "question": "wife",
      "answer": "wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "wild",
      "answer": "wild"
    },
    {
      "question": "will",
      "answer": "will"
    },
    {
      "question": "wind",
      "answer": "wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "wine",
      "answer": "wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "wing",
      "answer": "wing"
    },
    {
      "question": "wink",
      "answer": "wink"
    },
    {
      "question": "wipe",
      "answer": "wipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "wire",
      "answer": "wire"
    },
    {
      "question": "wise",
      "answer": "wise"
    },
    {
      "question": "wish",
      "answer": "wish"
    },
    {
      "question": "with",
      "answer": "with"
    },
    {
      "question": "wive",
      "answer": "wive"
    },
    {
      "question": "wolf",
      "answer": "wolf"
    },
    {
      "question": "womb",
      "answer": "womb"
    },
    {
      "question": "wont",
      "answer": "wont"
    },
    {
      "question": "wood",
      "answer": "wood"
    },
    {
      "question": "wool",
      "answer": "wool"
    },
    {
      "question": "word",
      "answer": "word"
    },
    {
      "question": "work",
      "answer": "work"
    },
    {
      "question": "worm",
      "answer": "worm"
    },
    {
      "question": "worn",
      "answer": "worn"
    },
    {
      "question": "wrap",
      "answer": "wrap"
    },
    {
      "question": "writ",
      "answer": "writ"
    },
    {
      "question": "yard",
      "answer": "yard"
    },
    {
      "question": "yarn",
      "answer": "yarn"
    },
    {
      "question": "yawn",
      "answer": "yawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "yaws",
      "answer": "yaws"
    },
    {
      "question": "yeah",
      "answer": "yeah"
    },
    {
      "question": "year",
      "answer": "year"
    },
    {
      "question": "yell",
      "answer": "yell"
    },
    {
      "question": "yoga",
      "answer": "yoga"
    },
    {
      "question": "yoke",
      "answer": "yoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "yolk",
      "answer": "yolk"
    },
    {
      "question": "your",
      "answer": "your"
    },
    {
      "question": "zeal",
      "answer": "zeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "zero",
      "answer": "zero"
    },
    {
      "question": "zest",
      "answer": "zest"
    },
    {
      "question": "zinc",
      "answer": "zinc"
    },
    {
      "question": "zone",
      "answer": "zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "lots",
      "answer": "lots"
    },
    {
      "question": "okay",
      "answer": "okay"
    },
    {
      "question": "user",
      "answer": "user"
    },
    {
      "question": "math",
      "answer": "math"
    },
    {
      "question": "mall",
      "answer": "mall"
    },
    {
      "question": "odds",
      "answer": "odds"
    },
    {
      "question": "scan",
      "answer": "scan"
    },
    {
      "question": "exam",
      "answer": "exam"
    },
    {
      "question": "coup",
      "answer": "coup"
    },
    {
      "question": "atop",
      "answer": "atop"
    },
    {
      "question": "disc",
      "answer": "disc"
    }
  ]
}